Finding Aid for the Donald Kalish Papers LSC.0578
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Baton: General logic, undated (Box 106, Folder 9)
- Thompson's suggestion, undated (Box 106, Folder 10)
  Notes on Russel (Mclendon) Notes on Theory of Types (PM)
- Some proofs, 1941 (Box 106, Folder 11)
- Logics, definitions and proofs, undated (Box 106, Folder 12)
- Philosophy 113 (Spring), 1952 (Box 106, Folder 13)
- Logic, 1941 (Box 106, Folder 14)
- The mates system, undated (Box 106, Folder 15)
- Philosophy 241: Montague's notes (Spring), 1956 (Box 106, Folder 16)
- Philosophy 241: Montague (Spring), 1958 (Box 106, Folder 17)
- Montague's seminar and Godel Theory (Fall), 1961 (Box 106, Folder 18)
- Ontological argument, 1947 (Box 106, Folder 19)
- Mate's proof of a geometrical problem by Marhenke, 1947 (Box 106, Folder 20)
- Notes on formal logic by Cooley, 1948 June (Box 106, Folder 21)
- Articles germane to logic, 1937-1946 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- C.C. Chang notes on theory of models seminar, undated (Box 107, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 240: Notes from Montauge's set theory (Spring), 1962 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- Notes on Hilbert's e-symbol, 1946 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- Some proofs, 9-14 of PM, undated (Box 107, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 6B texts and some proofs 1-5, 1942-1943 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 162: V. Milosevich, 1960-1963 (Box 107, Folder 7)
- Automatic proof procedure for quantifier calculus, Mr. Klugh, 1958-1962 (Box 107, Folder 8)
- Lung-Ock Chung paper: "The Sequentzen Kalkul for Relevent Entailment [A Preliminary Report]", undated (Box 107, Folder 9)
- Supres learning models, undated (Box 107, Folder 10)
- "Empirical Explorations of the Logic Theory Machine: A Case Study in Heuristics" (Revised), 1957 March (Box 107, Folder 11)
- "A Linear Learning Model for a Continuum of Responses" by Patrick Suppes, 1958 October (Box 107, Folder 12)
- Recent papers by Benbow Ritchie, 1962 (Box 107, Folder 13)
- "Unate Truth Function," R. McNaughton, 1961 March (Box 108, Folder 1)
- "A Proof Method for Quantification Theory: Its Justification and Realization," P.C. Gilmore, 1960 January (Box 108, Folder 2)
- Toward mechanical math, H. Wang, undated (Box 108, Folder 3)
- A new law of universal gravitation, Alvin C. Sugar, 1963 February (Box 108, Folder 4)
- "The Role of Subjective Probability and Utility In Decision Making," Patrick Suppes, 1955 June (Box 108, Folder 5)
- "Computational Methods for the Simplification of Truth Formulas," Aviezri S. Fraenkel, undated (Box 108, Folder 6)
- Root metaphors, Ritchie, 1940 February (Box 108, Folder 7)
- Text on two-place predicates and fitting sequences by Herman Rubin and Suppes, 1955 June (Box 108, Folder 8)
- "Group Structures and Communication Networks in Terms of Mathematical Theory of Graphs," Harary and Norman, undated (Box 108, Folder 9)
- Algebraic synthesis of logical feedback nets, Jeffrey, 1954 October (Box 108, Folder 10)
- Mathematical models in the social sciences, Kenneth J. Arrow, undated (Box 108, Folder 11)
- Computable numbers, A. M. Turing, undated (Box 108, Folder 12)
- Some comments on operationism, A. Grunbaum, undated (Box 108, Folder 13)
- Paper by Rubin, undated (Box 108, Folder 14)
- Communist teachers, Tussman (Philosophy Department, UC Berkeley), undated (Box 108, Folder 15)
- Quine's mathematical logic, A. Glathe, undated (Box 108, Folder 16)
- Decision procedure and functional calculus, N. Martin, undated (Box 108, Folder 17)
- Papers by Von Heinrich Behmann, undated (Box 108, Folder 18)
- Description in psychchology, Ritchie, 1943 (Box 108, Folder 19)
- Philosophy 1C, undated (Box 108, Folder 20)
- Publications: Numerical analysis, undated (Box 108, Folder 21)
- Physicalism and related topics, Carnap, 1954 (Box 108, Folder 22)
- Counter-factual conditionals, R. Schock, undated (Box 109, Folder 1)
- Electric shock treatment, Murry Korngold, 1953 June (Box 109, Folder 2)
- Theory of perpetratorship, Kotarbinaski, undated (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Comments on Hawkin's manuscript, undated (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Smart's "History of Logic", undated (Box 109, Folder 5)
- Nagel's logic sans ontology, undated (Box 109, Folder 6)
- Kaplan: "What Good is Truth?", undated (Box 109, Folder 7)
- "What does the First Amendment Mean?", undated (Box 109, Folder 8)
- "The Philosophy of Science of Logical Empiricism," Herbert Feigl, 1954 August (Box 109, Folder 9)
- "Introductory Remarks" in Causality in Modern Physics, M. Schlick, 1931 February (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Rooser exams and exercises, undated (Box 109, Folder 11)
- "A Logical Calculus of the Ideas Immanent in Nervous Activity," McCulloch and Pitts, 1943 (Box 109, Folder 12)
- "Foundations of Biology," F. Mainx, 1955 (Box 109, Folder 13)
- Wisdom: The Philosophical Enter, 1958 January (Box 109, Folder 14)
- "What can Philosophy Determine?" Aristotelian Society, 1936 (Box 109, Folder 15)
- Travis' dissertation proposal, undated (Box 109, Folder 16)
- Outline of Weschler's course (Spring), 1957 (Box 109, Folder 17)
- L.C. Powell, UCLA Chapter of the American Association of University Professors, 1959 March (Box 109, Folder 18)
- Hypothetical robots and neuro-economy, J. T. Culberston, 1952 April (Box 109, Folder 19)
- Correspondence and news clippings related to Concerned Faculty on Iraq, 1970-1992 (Box 109, Folder 20)
- Otto Kraus correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- Non-academic staff salaries and promotions, 1964-1967 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Notes for letters of appraisal, Gunderson, Savage, Sobel, undated (Box 110, Folder 3)
- Curriculum, Kalish-Kaplan, 1966-1968 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Correspondence with Monty Furth, 1965-1966 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Correspondence with David Kaplan, 1965-1966 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Semantics, modal logic, and probability, David Lewis, undated (Box 110, Folder 7)
- "Quine on Propositional Attitudes," David Kaplan, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 8)
- Space Committee, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 9)
- Comments on papers by Long and Furth for appraisal and promotion, undated (Box 110, Folder 10)
- Expenses incurred for department, 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 11)
- Walter Burford (Winter), 1969 (Box 110, Folder 12)
- Kenneth Mills, 1966-1969 (Box 110, Folder 13)
- Angela Davis, 1968-1969, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 14)
- Institution correspondence, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 15)
- Incidental correspondence (Winter), 1969 (Box 110, Folder 16)
- Albert Gene Mosley, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 17)
- Assorted correspondence, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 18)
- Daily Bruin, 1983 May 4 (Box 110, Folder 19)
- Assorted correspondence, 1967 (Box 110, Folder 20)
- Department during Angela Davis' time, 1968-1970 (Box 110, Folder 21)
- Committee C, 1956-1959 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- High schools, 1958-1959 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Miss Griffith, undated (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Comments on Alex's manuscript, undated (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1955 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- John Wisdom correspondence, 1959 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Donald Kalish bibliography, undated (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Letters of invitation for bio-bibliography and other uses, 1966-1967 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- Letters of invitation for bio-bibliography and other uses, 1964-1965 (Box 111, Folder 9)
- Letters of invitation for bio-bibliography and other uses, 1965-1966 (Box 111, Folder 10)
- Teaching materials, outline, doctoral candidates resumes, and course evaluations, 1964-1967 (Box 111, Folder 11)
- Letters of invitation for bio-bibliography and other uses, 1967-1968 (Box 111, Folder 12)
- Promotion material bio-bibliographical staff, 1955-1972 (Box 111, Folder 13)
- Articulation conference minutes (Spring), 1964 (Box 111, Folder 14)
- Department meetings, 1963-1964 (Box 111, Folder 15)
- Baldwin Hills Committee of Concern (Spring), 1967 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Methodist church talk (Spring), 1967 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- KLAC appearance (Spring), 1967 (Box 112, Folder 3)
- Valley Unitarian Church Sunday service, undated (Box 112, Folder 4)
- Student power talk, Friends of Monterrey Park Library), 1967 (Box 112, Folder 5)
- KPFK, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 6)
- Notes on talks for anti-war movement, 1967-1968 (Box 112, Folder 7)
- Vietnam commencement Tucson, 1968-1970 (Box 112, Folder 8)
- Studio City CDC, 1967 August 16 (Box 112, Folder 9)
- CDC club, 1967 September 1 (Box 112, Folder 10)
- Which Way for Peace Movement, 1967 August 8 (Box 112, Folder 11)
- Cal State Fullerton, 1967 September (Box 112, Folder 12)
- St. Thomas More Law Society (Fall), 1967 (Box 112, Folder 13)
- Palisades High School talk, 1968 April (Box 112, Folder 14)
- Don Freed, 1967 November (Box 112, Folder 15)
- Police-community relations conference (Spring), 1968 (Box 112, Folder 16)
- Long Beach Citizens for Peace, 1968 January (Box 112, Folder 17)
- 19th District CDC Convention, 1968 February (Box 112, Folder 18)
- La Crescenta Valley Methodist Church (Winter), 1968 (Box 112, Folder 19)
- La Tijera Methodist Church, 1967-1968 (Box 112, Folder 20)
- VIVA and Young Republicans, 1968 January (Box 112, Folder 21)
- Discussion at Hershey Hall, 1968 January 18 (Box 112, Folder 22)
- Channel 28 Discovery, 1967-1968 (Box 112, Folder 23)
- Evening Chapter Women for Legislative Action, 1967 December (Box 112, Folder 24)
- Ethical Culture Society of Los Angeles, 1967 (Box 112, Folder 25)
- B'nai B'rith, 1967 March (Box 112, Folder 26)
- Open for discussion on KTLA, 1967 July (Box 112, Folder 27)
- South Bay Vietnam (Summer), 1967 August (Box 112, Folder 28)
- Civil disobedience, 1967 August (Box 113, Folder 1)
- United Presbyterian Church, 1967 (Box 113, Folder 2)
- PRIDE (Summer), 1967 (Box 113, Folder 3)
- ACLU talk, 1967 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- Leo Baeck Temple (Summer), 1967 (Box 113, Folder 5)
- KFWB Radio perspective on peace movement, 1967 July (Box 113, Folder 6)
- Fairfax High School (Spring), 1967 (Box 113, Folder 7)
- Student protest and rights, and college deans, 1967 May (Box 113, Folder 8)
- National Issues Forum, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 9)
- Jefferson Club debate, 1968 May (Box 113, Folder 10)
- Regent's Scholars lunch and talk, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 11)
- Rights and Riots Conference, 1968 May 11 (Box 113, Folder 12)
- Urban Affairs Conference (Spring), 1968 (Box 113, Folder 13)
- Temple Beth Hall, 1967 November (Box 113, Folder 14)
- Hamilton High (Fall), 1967 (Box 113, Folder 15)
- Vietnam Congressional hearings, 1967 November (Box 113, Folder 16)
- Panel at Reiber Hall, 1967 November (Box 113, Folder 17)
- Long Beach State newspaper clippings, 1967 (Box 113, Folder 18)
- Northeast Peace Group, 1967 November (Box 113, Folder 19)
- Campus psychologists, 1967 November (Box 113, Folder 20)
- Peace Action Day, American Mental Health Professionals, Loyola, 1967-1968 (Box 113, Folder 21)
- Trojan Democrats (Fall), 1967 (Box 113, Folder 22)
- Communications, 1982-1986 (Box 113, Folder 23)
- Middle East newspaper clippings and correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 113, Folder 24)
- American Jews opposition to Israeli aggression newspaper clippings, 1982 (Box 113, Folder 25)
- Middle East issues newspaper clippings, 1982 (Box 113, Folder 26)
- Nuclear weapons and defense expenses newspaper clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 114, Folder 1)
- Concerned Faculty statement of purpose, undated (Box 114, Folder 2)
- UCS communications, 1981-1982 (Box 114, Folder 3)
- Ground Zero: Perspective, 1981-1982 (Box 114, Folder 4)
- UCS, 1981 (Box 114, Folder 5)
- Freeze campaign, 1981-1982 (Box 114, Folder 6)
- Fundraising effort (11/11), 1981 December (Box 114, Folder 7)
- Harcourt Brace Correspondence (I), 1978-1983 (Box 114, Folder 8-9)
- Central America statement signature, 1983 March (Box 115, Folder 1)
- Newspaper clippings on racism, 1969-1970 (Box 115, Folder 2)
- "The Conspiracy," Mobe Pac, 1970 April (Box 115, Folder 3)
- JC Board, 1969-1970 (Box 115, Folder 4)
- People's Justice and Law College, 1975-1976 (Box 115, Folder 6)
- Deportation of Vietnamese students newspaper clippings, 1974 (Box 115, Folder 7)
- War in Southeast Asia newspaper clippings, 1974 (Box 115, Folder 8)
- Richard Nixon and impeachment newspaper clippings, 1974 (Box 115, Folder 9)
- Newspaper clippings on other movements, 1974 (Box 115, Folder 10)
- Constitutional Rights Foundation (Fall), 1972 (Box 115, Folder 11)
- Additional articles, 1971 (Box 115, Folder 12)
- Jeanne Knutson, 1971 (Box 115, Folder 13)
- "Dissent and Disorder" report on Peace Parade in Chicago, 1968 August 1 (Box 115, Folder 14)
- Lerner, Michael and monthly review, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 15)
- Radical Education Project, 1966 (Box 115, Folder 16)
- The Police and Race Relations, 1966 (Box 115, Folder 17)
- Repression in America, undated (Box 115, Folder 18)
- The Monitor and the Crowd, undated (Box 116, Folder 1)
- "Analysis of the 13th Report of the State Senate Fact-finding Subcommittee on Un-American Activities", 1965 October (Box 116, Folder 2)
- Photographs of the Atlanta Rebellion, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 3)
- Sihanouk's message to compatriots and North Vietnam statement on Cambodia coup (Spring), 1970 (Box 116, Folder 4)
- Underdogs vs upperdogs, James Peck, 1969 (Box 116, Folder 5)
- "Black Reparations: Two Views," Michael Harrington, undated (Box 116, Folder 6)
- "The Case for Professionalism," Robert Brustein, undated (Box 116, Folder 7)
- Military Intelligence, 1970 September (Box 116, Folder 8)
- "Faculty Mediation of Student War Protests," William R. Morgan, undated (Box 116, Folder 9)
- "American Escalation in Laos," Richard R. Fernandez, undated (Box 116, Folder 10)
- New West magazine (Spring), 1967 (Box 116, Folder 11)
- "The US in a Revolutionary World," Robert H. Simmons, 1968 April 6 (Box 116, Folder 12)
- "An Outline History of Vietnam," Adam Schesch, 1965 (Box 116, Folder 13)
- The Student Mobilizer, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 14)
- Political prisoners, 1971-1972 (Box 116, Folder 15)
- "The Long March", 1972 (Box 116, Folder 16)
- Films, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 17)
- Speakers, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 18)
- Russian authors, 1967-1968 (Box 116, Folder 19)
- Center for Constitutional Rights, New York, 1972 (Box 116, Folder 20)
- Los Angeles Anti-War Defense Committee, Red Tide, Fidelio caucus, 1972 (Box 116, Folder 21)
- Bradley advert and receipt (Spring), 1973 (Box 116, Folder 22)
- Medical aid to Indochina and MCHR, 1972-1973 (Box 116, Folder 23)
- "Set the Date" campaign, 1972 (Box 117, Folder 1)
- AAUP and Morris Starsky, 1971-1973 (Box 117, Folder 2)
- AAUP, 1972-1976 (Box 117, Folder 3)
- Response to Los Angeles Times article (Fall), 1972 (Box 117, Folder 4)
- George Jackson pamphlet, 1972 (Box 117, Folder 5)
- People's Action Union for Peace and Justice newspaper clippings, 1973-1974 (Box 117, Folder 6)
- Stop Bombing rally newspaper clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 117, Folder 7)
- Conspiracy event (Winter), 1970 (Box 117, Folder 8)
- Anti-war adverts in Daily Bruin, 1971-1972 (Box 117, Folder 9)
- Newspaper clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 117, Folder 10)
- "March Against Death" poster, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 11)
- Los Angeles Times articles, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 12)
- Brother Crook, 1970 (Box 117, Folder 13)
- Ramsey Clark Tour, Century Plaza demonstration, and Peace Week at UCLA, 1972 (Box 117, Folder 14)
- Anti-war newspaper clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 117, Folder 15)
- Allen and the BSU newspaper clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 118, Folder 1-2)
- "Normative Theories of Confidence," Paul Weirich dissertation, 1975 January (Box 118, Folder 3)
- Paul Weirich, 1973-1974 (Box 118, Folder 4)
- Dan Wikler, 1975 (Box 118, Folder 5)
- Daniel Shartin's proposition, 1975 January (Box 118, Folder 6)
- Nino Cocchiarella, 1974-1975 (Box 118, Folder 7)
- Committee of Clergy and Laymen Concerned About Vietnam, 1968 (Box 119, Folder 1)
- Paul Weirich, undated (Box 119, Folder 2)
- "Probability and Utility for Decision Theory," Paul Weirich, 1976 November (Box 119, Folder 3)
- Morals and society, 1968-1971 (Box 119, Folder 4)
- Peoples College of Law, 1978 April (Box 119, Folder 5)
- A meeting of conscience in support of Spock, 1968 January (Box 119, Folder 6)
- Oakland Community School, 1975 (Box 119, Folder 7)
- Chicago and other clippings, 1968-1970 (Box 119, Folder 8)
- ACLU, 1979 (Box 119, Folder 9)
- "Completeness of sentential logic in the strong sense", undated (Box 119, Folder 10)
- Revision by Quine of #28, 1955 December (Box 119, Folder 11)
- Philosophy 184A (Spring), 1956 (Box 119, Folder 12)
- Metatheorem 3 notes on proof (Spring), 1956 (Box 119, Folder 13)
- Problems in CN, natural deduction calculus, undated (Box 119, Folder 14)
- Chapter IV, "Metalogic of Sentential Calculi," Montague-Kalish, undated (Box 119, Folder 15)
- Stencils 184A (Spring), 1956 (Box 119, Folder 16)
- Paper: "If 0 th. of ND, then 0 formal th.", undated (Box 119, Folder 17)
- Philosophy 184 final exam, 1954 June (Box 119, Folder 18)
- Benson Mates notes on sentential and predicate calculus, 1949-1953 (Box 119, Folder 19)
- Student Mobility Committee correspondence, 1969 (Box 120, Folder 1)
- Jobs with Peace, 1992 (Box 120, Folder 2)
- Newspaper clippings and correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 120, Folder 3)
- El Salvador/Nicaragua conference, 1993 June (Box 120, Folder 4)
- The Voice of Faculty newsletter, University of California Academic Senate, LA Division, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 5)
- Concerned Faculty newsletter, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 6)
- Concerned Faculty on police abuse and violence, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 7)
- SCITCA members, newspaper clippings on South America, undated (Box 120, Folder 8)
- Materials on Woman's Study Center, correspondence from Flannigan, Physicians for Human Rights, 1989-1992 (Box 120, Folder 9)
- Forest of National Reconciliation (El Salvador), 1993 (Box 120, Folder 10)
- Concerned Faculty: Faculty center correspondence, 1993 May (Box 120, Folder 11)
- Concerned Faculty: UCLA (Winter), 1990 (Box 120, Folder 12)
- Concerned Faculty: UCLA (Spring), 1990 (Box 120, Folder 13)
- Concerned Faculty: UCLA (Fall), 1990 (Box 120, Folder 14)
- Carecen, seventh annual dinner booklet, 1991 (Box 120, Folder 15)
- Concerned Faculty meeting, 1991 May (Box 120, Folder 16)
- "The Olive Branch: A Calendar of Events about the Middle East", 1991 May (Box 120, Folder 17)
- Jobs with peace, 1991 (Box 120, Folder 18)
- Information about Concerned Faculty, 1986-1991 (Box 120, Folder 19)
- Pro-anti choice legislation, Jerry Hoffman, 1991 (Box 120, Folder 20)
- "The Establishment", 1967 February (Box 120, Folder 21)
- From House of Representatives, Henry Gonzalez on terms of impeachment, 1991 January (Box 121, Folder 1)
- Correspondence and newspaper clippings on El Salvador 1990, Mandela's US Congress address (Box 121, Folder 2)
- Academic Senate and APBAC, 1993-1994 (Box 121, Folder 3)
- Address book, undated (Box 121, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 134, 1981 (Box 121, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 134: Introduction to set theory and syllabus (Spring), 1980 (Box 121, Folder 6)
- "Zermelo: Proof of Well-Ordering and Isomorphism of ax a and a for infinite ordinal a" (Winter), 1977 (Box 121, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 134: Flashcards and records (Fall), 1970 (Box 121, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 134, 1976 (Box 121, Folder 9)
- Set theory discussion with Martin Balo (Summer), 1977 (Box 121, Folder 10)
- GCH and AC Specker article, 1954 (Box 121, Folder 11)
- "For a notebook on elementary theorems on the finite and infinite" (Fall), 1973 (Box 121, Folder 12)
- Axiom of choice, undated (Box 121, Folder 13)
- "Elementary Equivalents to A. of Choice: Old Notes on Hartog and Comparibility Implies A of C" (Winter), 1973 (Box 121, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 134: Lecture notes (Fall), 1976 (Box 121, Folder 15)
- Philosophy 134: Grades and papers (Winter), 1970 (Box 121, Folder 16)
- Philosophy 184A: Set theory and logic (Fall), 1961 (Box 122, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 134: Set theory homework (Winter), 1971 (Box 122, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 134: Set theory problems (Winter), 1974 (Box 122, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 134: Set theory records (Spring), 1972 (Box 122, Folder 4)
- Suppes' proof of enumeration theorem, 1975 June (Box 122, Folder 5)
- Nino's set theory examination (Spring), 1962 (Box 122, Folder 6)
- Zorn's Lemma implies axiom of choice, and Richard Taurek report (Fall), 1961 (Box 122, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 134: Set theory, theorems, and proofs (Fall), 1976 (Box 122, Folder 8)
- Philosophy M221A: Syllabus and handouts (Spring), 1976 (Box 122, Folder 9)
- Formalization of Jech's proof, undated (Box 122, Folder 10)
- Fitzgerald's proof of Zorn's Lemma, undated (Box 122, Folder 11)
- Exponential again, Chris Freiling, 1978 June (Box 122, Folder 12)
- Zordinals, undated (Box 122, Folder 13)
- Elegant proofs and easy ways, undated (Box 122, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 134: Notes, Rosser Lemma proof, and denumerable union theorem (Winter), 1976 (Box 122, Folder 15)
- Philosophy 134: Notes and handouts, 1976 (Box 122, Folder 16)
- Philosophy 134: Notes and handouts (Fall), 1985 (Box 122, Folder 17)
- Material on w x w ~ w, 1975-1985 (Box 122, Folder 18)
- Subset of an ordinal, 1973-1981 (Box 122, Folder 19)
- Denumerable questions, 1975-1985 (Box 122, Folder 20)
- Philosophy 134: Set theory, references, theorems, notes (Winter), 1971 (Box 123, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 134 (Spring), 1972 (Box 123, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 134: Set theory, and natural numbers, undated (Box 123, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 134: Set theory preliminary, cardinals, problems and solutions (Spring), 1960 (Box 123, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 134: Set theory lecture notes (Spring), 1980 (Box 123, Folder 5)
- Peano's arithmetic without axiom of regularity, undated (Box 123, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 134 (Winter), 1978 (Box 123, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 134: Records and set theory (Winter), 1978 (Box 123, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 221A: Set theory and records (Spring), 1978 (Box 123, Folder 9)
- "Choice Function Implies Zorn, Zorn Implies Well-Ordering", 1975 May (Box 123, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 134 (Spring), 1984 (Box 123, Folder 11)
- Philosophy 134: Records (Fall), 1982 (Box 123, Folder 12)
- History of set theory, Johnson, undated (Box 123, Folder 13)
- "Set Theory from Cantor to Chen," D. Van Dalen, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 134: Burali-Ford paradox, Georg Cantor mathematics, and philosophy of infinite, undated (Box 123, Folder 15)
- Set theory (Spring), 1976 (Box 123, Folder 16)
- Set theory: Well-ordering in Zarmelo, comparability proofs, 1975-1977 (Box 124, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 134: Theorem list by Brad Berlin, partition theorem proof (Fall), 1985 (Box 124, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 134: Introduction to set theory, exam, student papers, and records (Fall), 1985 (Box 124, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 134: Syllabus (Fall), 1985 (Box 124, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 134: Introduction to set theory and syllabus, undated (Box 124, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 134: Syllabus and other materials (Fall), 1985 (Box 124, Folder 6)
- W X W ~ W proofs and comments, 1975-1980 (Box 124, Folder 7)
- Natural numbers, on and related to induction, undated (Box 124, Folder 8)
- Induction for 184A, undated (Box 124, Folder 9)
- Copies of current preparationist, and dedekind finite material, 1985 July (Box 124, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 134: Set theory (Winter), 1981 (Box 124, Folder 11)
- Philosophy 134: Notes for lectures, and natural numbers (Winter), 1981 (Box 124, Folder 12)
- Philosophy 134: Thoughts on axiomatization (Winter), 1981 (Box 124, Folder 13)
- Philosophy 134: Syllabus up to natural numbers (Winter), 1981 (Box 124, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 134: Natural numbers, syllabus, and proofs (Winter), 1981 (Box 124, Folder 15)
- Philosophy 134: Materials from introduction to set theory, undated (Box 124, Folder 16)
- "Unselling the War to Max P" magazine article, 1972 (Box 125, Folder 1)
- "Project Air War: Documentation of US Bombing of Dikes and Dams in Vietnam" newspaper clipping, 1972 (Box 125, Folder 2)
- Anti-war activities against Nixon for McGovern (Box 125, Folder 3)
- Anti-war posters, newspaper clippings, and pamphlets, 1972-1973 (Box 125, Folder 4)
- Newspaper clippings on the Vietnam War, 1972-1973 (Box 125, Folder 5)